[
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-21",
        "QUESTION": "Naturally hairy, often wet. Searching for wood that I can get. What am I ?",
        "ANSWER": "beaver"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-22",
        "QUESTION": "Four letters stand to make my name. Should 2 be taken, 4 remains. And should they take away 1 more, my meaning will be as before.",
        "ANSWER": "Five"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-23",
        "QUESTION": "You can swallow me, but I can consume you too. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "Pride"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-24",
        "QUESTION": "We are 16 in total, but can never be a king, what are we? ",
        "ANSWER": "Pawns"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-25",
        "QUESTION": " I wield power, yet I'm not a king; my influence spreads, but I have no wings. In me, you'll find wisdom, folly, and more; I'm passed between hands and through many doors. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "coin"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-26",
        "QUESTION": " With no legs, I slither and slide; with no lungs, I breathe deep inside. A master of disguise, I can change my hue; I'm both predator and prey, to name just a few. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "octopus"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-27",
        "QUESTION": " I dance in the night, but fade in the day; I'm never held captive, try as you may. An illusion of sorts, yet there's nothing to hold; I'm often pursued, but I'm never controlled. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": " dream"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-28",
        "QUESTION": " Though I have no heart, I can still pump; no legs, but I climb and jump. I'm always moving, never idle, and if you chase me, you'll be in a cycle. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": " wave"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-29",
        "QUESTION": " I come in pairs, yet I'm never the same; a crucial player in a complex game. You use me daily, yet seldom with care, and without me, your path would lead nowhere. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "glasses"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-30",
        "QUESTION": " I bind and divide, yet I have no hands; I can mark the passing of life's many sands. Invisible, I hold strong, but one small tear can make me fall and disappear. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "memory"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-03-31",
        "QUESTION": " In the darkness, I bring light, but not from the sun or moon's sight. I'm ancient and young, with no end or start; you'll find me in stories, poems, and art. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "fire"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-01",
        "QUESTION": " I am your guard, your armor, your shield; with me by your side, you'll never yield. I'm always there, but seldom shown; my strength depends on you alone. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "Courage"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-02",
        "QUESTION": " I'm not alive, but I can grow; I lack a mouth, yet I can flow. I can be tamed or run wild, and my form is often beguiled. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "river"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-03",
        "QUESTION": " I can be vast and infinite or small and confined; I may hold treasures, secrets, and memories combined. I can be locked, but I have no key; only you can truly set me free. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "mind"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-04",
        "QUESTION": "We are 16 in total, but can never be a king, what are we? ",
        "ANSWER": "Pawns"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-05",
        "QUESTION": "At half I am only some. When I'm full, people will turn my way. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "handsome"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-06",
        "QUESTION": "If you have it and you show it to other people, I’m gone. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "Secret"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-07",
        "QUESTION": "What spends all the time on the floor but never gets dirty?",
        "ANSWER": "Shadow"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-08",
        "QUESTION": "What has four fingers and thumb, but it is not living?",
        "ANSWER": "glove"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-09",
        "QUESTION": "What is it that no one wants, but no one wants to lose?",
        "ANSWER": "lawsuit"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-10",
        "QUESTION": "I have cities, but no houses. I have mountains, but no trees. I have water, but no fish. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "map"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-11",
        "QUESTION": "What loses its head in the morning and gets it back at night?",
        "ANSWER": "pillow"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-12",
        "QUESTION": "Naturally hairy, often wet. Searching for wood that I can get. What am I ?",
        "ANSWER": "beaver"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-13",
        "QUESTION": "Four letters stand to make my name. Should 2 be taken, 4 remains. And should they take away 1 more, my meaning will be as before.",
        "ANSWER": "Five"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-14",
        "QUESTION": "You can swallow me, but I can consume you too. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "Pride"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-15",
        "QUESTION": "We are 16 in total, but can never be a king, what are we? ",
        "ANSWER": "Pawns"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-16",
        "QUESTION": "At half I am only some. When I'm full, people will turn my way. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "handsome"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-17",
        "QUESTION": "If you have it and you show it to other people, I’m gone. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "Secret"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-18",
        "QUESTION": "What spends all the time on the floor but never gets dirty?",
        "ANSWER": "Shadow"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-19",
        "QUESTION": "What has four fingers and thumb, but it is not living?",
        "ANSWER": "glove"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-20",
        "QUESTION": "What is it that no one wants, but no one wants to lose?",
        "ANSWER": "lawsuit"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-21",
        "QUESTION": "I have cities, but no houses. I have mountains, but no trees. I have water, but no fish. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "map"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-22",
        "QUESTION": "What loses its head in the morning and gets it back at night?",
        "ANSWER": "pillow"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-23",
        "QUESTION": " I wield power, yet I'm not a king; my influence spreads, but I have no wings. In me, you'll find wisdom, folly, and more; I'm passed between hands and through many doors. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "coin"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-24",
        "QUESTION": " With no legs, I slither and slide; with no lungs, I breathe deep inside. A master of disguise, I can change my hue; I'm both predator and prey, to name just a few. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "octopus"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-25",
        "QUESTION": " I dance in the night, but fade in the day; I'm never held captive, try as you may. An illusion of sorts, yet there's nothing to hold; I'm often pursued, but I'm never controlled. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": " dream"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-26",
        "QUESTION": " Though I have no heart, I can still pump; no legs, but I climb and jump. I'm always moving, never idle, and if you chase me, you'll be in a cycle. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": " wave"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-27",
        "QUESTION": " I come in pairs, yet I'm never the same; a crucial player in a complex game. You use me daily, yet seldom with care, and without me, your path would lead nowhere. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "glasses"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-28",
        "QUESTION": " I bind and divide, yet I have no hands; I can mark the passing of life's many sands. Invisible, I hold strong, but one small tear can make me fall and disappear. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "memory"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-29",
        "QUESTION": " In the darkness, I bring light, but not from the sun or moon's sight. I'm ancient and young, with no end or start; you'll find me in stories, poems, and art. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "fire"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-04-30",
        "QUESTION": " I am your guard, your armor, your shield; with me by your side, you'll never yield. I'm always there, but seldom shown; my strength depends on you alone. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "Courage"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-05-01",
        "QUESTION": " I'm not alive, but I can grow; I lack a mouth, yet I can flow. I can be tamed or run wild, and my form is often beguiled. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "river"
    },
    {
        "DATE": "2023-05-02",
        "QUESTION": " I can be vast and infinite or small and confined; I may hold treasures, secrets, and memories combined. I can be locked, but I have no key; only you can truly set me free. What am I?",
        "ANSWER": "mind"
    }
]